<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on BSIDES Fort Wayne</title>
        <link>//localhost:1313/posts/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on BSIDES Fort Wayne</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 09:11:11 -0500</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        
        <item>
            <title>Tickets-Available-2025</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2025/01/tickets-available-2025/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 09:11:11 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2025/01/tickets-available-2025/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;BSides Fort Wayne on &lt;strong&gt;Saturday, June 7, 2025 at
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.pfw.edu/wuo&#34;&gt;Walb Student Union&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Tickets for BSidesFortWayne are available now! The regular price is $30.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grab your ticket at &lt;a href=&#34;https://bsidesfortwayne2025.eventbrite.com/&#34;&gt;Eventbrite&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>BSides Fort Wayne on <strong>Saturday, June 7, 2025 at
<a href="https://www.pfw.edu/wuo">Walb Student Union</a></strong>.</p>
<p>Tickets for BSidesFortWayne are available now! The regular price is $30.</p>
<p>Grab your ticket at <a href="https://bsidesfortwayne2025.eventbrite.com/">Eventbrite</a>!</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Speakers-2024</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 01:02:48 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Come take a look at our exciting list of experts, leaders, and practitioners who are going to give us an amazing conference. If you haven’t bought your ticket yet, you will want to after this!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Come take a look at our exciting list of experts, leaders, and practitioners who are going to give us an amazing conference. If you haven’t bought your ticket yet, you will want to after this!</p>
<h2 id="john-strand---keynote-speaker">John Strand - Keynote Speaker</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2024/john-1024x1024-462x625.webp"
    alt="John Strand picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation-">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Keynote&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>John Strand has both consulted and taught hundreds of organizations in the areas of security, regulatory compliance, and penetration testing.  He is a coveted speaker and much loved SANS teacher. John is a contributor to the industry-shaping Penetration Testing Execution Standard and 20 Critical Controls frameworks.
<a href="https://www.blackhillsinfosec.com/team/john-strand/">https://www.blackhillsinfosec.com/team/john-strand/</a></p>
<h2 id="matt-hansen">Matt Hansen</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Matt%20Hansen.jpg"
    alt="Matt Hansen picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--1">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Beyond No: InfoSec&rsquo;s Role in Enterprise Success&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Matt is a Cloud Solution Architect at Microsoft who focuses on Azure Infrastructure and Security. He has been in the industry for 15 years as an Engineer and Architect, and serves as a Subject Matter Expert, Advisory Committee Member, and as a Professor for Cloud and Security Technologies. Matt holds over 50 industry certifications such as the CCSP, CISSP, Azure Security Engineer, Azure Network Engineer, and has held all versions of the Azure Solutions Architecture Certifications. Matt holds a B.S in Network Engineering and M.S in Engineering Management, and a M.S in Information Systems Security and an Executive Certificate in Cybersecurity Management.</p>
<h2 id="seif-hateb">Seif Hateb</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2024/seif.png"
    alt="Seif Hateb picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--2">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;The Three Musketeers, one of them is Purple&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Seif Hateb, a Security Engineering Leader, with over a decade of experience in spearheading large-scale projects and leading engineering teams in the cybersecurity field. His expertise spans across Cyber Defense, Cryptography, Product Security, AI and LLM Security. He has designed and implemented security solutions in various industries, including Software, Tech, Telecom and Healthcare.</p>
<h2 id="michael-miller">Michael Miller</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2024/michael-miller.jpg"
    alt="Michael Miller picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--3">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Building a Detection Engineering Lab at Home&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Michael is a cybersecurity leader, practitioner, speaker, and educator with 12+ years&rsquo; experience in enterprise cybersecurity, networking, server administration, and programming. He specializes in security engineering, automation, and operations. He is passionately focused on attracting, developing, and retaining talent, and advocates on improving diversity, equity, and inclusion in both his teams and the cybersecurity industry. He has a B.S. in Cybersecurity and Information Assurance from WGU, and an A.A.B. in Network Administration and Computer Programming from NSCC where he also sits as a member of the IT advisory board and is a part time instructor of cybersecurity courses. Michael holds a variety of industry certifications including the CISSP, CCSP, SSCP, GISP, CEH, ECES, and CySA+ just to name a few. Michael lives in Northwest Ohio with his wife and their two children. In his free time, he enjoys spending time with his wife and kids, traveling, cooking, public speaking, and tinkering with his home lab.</p>
<h2 id="rob-rodriguez">Rob Rodriguez</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2024/rob-rodriguez.jpg"
    alt="Rob Rodriguez picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--4">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Cutting Through The Noise: Lessons From a Decade of Electronic Warfare&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Rob Rodriguez is a cybersecurity professional with over 25 years of experience. Leveraging his diverse background in the Intelligence Community and cybersecurity, he provides valuable experience in securing sensitive systems and data. Dedicated to the next generation of Cybersecurity, Rob actively mentors aspiring cybersecurity professionals through initiatives like the Marine Corps Cyber Auxiliary and Veterati. Outside of his professional focus, Rob is a published author with several articles featured in various publications such as 2600 magazine. In his downtime, you will find him diving into a good book, playing guitar in his band, or his favorite, spending quality time with his wife and three sons.</p>
<h2 id="steve-saylor">Steve Saylor</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2024/steve-saylor.jpg"
    alt="Steve Saylor picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--5">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Winning the Battle for Budget&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Steve Saylor, an accomplished IT and Cybersecurity leader, brings over two decades of experience guiding a diverse number of organizations. His expertise lies in leading the process of planning, implementing, and securing business technology environments. Specializing in “translating the language of the server room to the language of the board room”, Steve has helped build and execute technology strategies and roadmaps for more than 60 companies in the healthcare, financial services, non-profit, and professional services fields.  Steve currently leads the IT and Cybersecurity Team at SYM Financial, a $4 billion investment advisory firm.  He holds several industry certifications, including the CISM and is active in the local cybersecurity community.</p>
<h2 id="chistian-ebel-orr">Chistian Ebel-Orr</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2024/Ebel-Orr.jpg"
    alt="Chistian Ebel-Orr picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--6">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Cyber Threats and Criminal Trends&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Technical Special Agent Christian Ebel-Orr has been with the Secret Service for 21 years. During that time, he has been assigned to the Counter Assault Team, Presidential Protective Division, Obama Protective Division, and the Indianapolis Field Office. He currently manages the Indianapolis Digital Forensics Lab and the Indiana Cyber Fraud Task Force.</p>
<h2 id="0ddj0bb">0DDJ0BB</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2024/Odd2-1.png"
    alt="0DDJ0BB picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--7">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Nothing Went to Plan….. Because You Didn’t Have a Plan&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>0DDJ0BB has been Blue since 2013. he has quickly risen from the ranks as an engineer, consultant, IR analyst, Vulnerability Management Lead, and Senior Director. His background in education, bio-sciences, finance, retail, manufacturing, and healthcare give him a unique view on what it takes to build an InfoSec program given limited resources. He is host of the Glass of 0J YouTube Channel and is a Founding member of CircleCityCon (RIP)</p>
<h2 id="dale-fay--meridith-russell-fay">Dale Fay &amp; Meridith Russell-Fay</h2>
<h5 id="presentation--8">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Hack Your Mind: Practical Mental Health Insights for Technical People&rdquo;</em></h5>
<h2 id="richard-rieben">Richard Rieben</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2024/richard-rieben.jpg"
    alt="Richard Rieben picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--9">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;The Audit: A Significant Emotional Event&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Richard Rieben is a Partner and HITRUST practice lead at Linford &amp; Co., where he leads audits and assessments covering various frameworks including HITRUST, SOC, CMMC, and NIST. With over 20 years of experience in IT and cybersecurity and various certifications including PMP, CISSP, GSNA, and CASP+, Richard is skilled in helping growing organizations achieve their information security and compliance goals. He holds a Bachelor of Science in Business Management and an MBA from Western Governors University. In his spare time Richard enjoys the outdoors and participates in the hobby of amateur radio, licensed as KE4WLE.</p>
<h2 id="alissa-dnsprincess">Alissa (DNSPrincess)</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2024/alissa.jpeg"
    alt="Alissa (DNSPrincess) picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--10">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Preventing and Recovering from Burnout&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>I’m a seasoned cybersecurity professional with over a decade of experience, specializing in cybersecurity solutions architecture and penetration testing. I’ve enjoyed a robust academic career and now apply my deep knowledge to practical challenges in the field. As a mentor, I guide aspiring tech professionals towards achieving their Security+ certification, leveraging my extensive experience to foster their growth. Beyond my professional life, I’m a devoted dog parent and a supportive friend, especially adept at navigating the complexities of burnout. My journey has not only been about advancing my own skills but also about uplifting others in their personal and professional endeavors.</p>
<h2 id="stephen-heindel">Stephen Heindel</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2024/stephen_heindel_headshot.jpg"
    alt="Stephen Heindel picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--11">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Leveling Up Your Scripting&rdquo;</em></h5>
<ul>
<li>Software engineer with over 10 years of experience across a multitude of commercial and consumer sectors.</li>
<li>Married 10 years to my beautiful wife Sarah and have two beautiful children</li>
<li>Currently working as head of software at Rogo Ag, formerly worked for the excellent Fort Wayne software firm Logikos. Before Logikos worked for API Alliance in Huntertown.</li>
<li>Technical experience includes a wide variety of programming applications and platforms</li>
<li>Have worked across a multitude of commercial and consumer sectors, including audio electronics, refrigeration, air conditioning, building supply, medical equipment, agriculture, robotics, and self-driving</li>
<li>Worked in an electronics capacity designing and debugging integrated circuits for production deployments and test fixtures</li>
<li>Worked on production code in over 10 different programming languages across all major operating systems</li>
<li>Deployed and managed applications on all three Big Cloud providers, including several smaller ones</li>
<li>Specialize in broad system architectures, especially as it relates to IoT</li>
<li>Passionate about educating others and sparking joy in programming</li>
<li>Hobbies include woodworking, home renovation, and 3D printing</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="harish-santhanalakshmi-ganesan">Harish Santhanalakshmi Ganesan</h2>
<h5 id="presentation--12">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Hacking AI/ML for fun and profit&rdquo;</em></h5>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Tickets &amp; Training Available</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2024/03/tickets-training-available/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:04:36 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2024/03/tickets-training-available/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Tickets for BSidesFortWayne are available now! The regular price is $25.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grab your ticket at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/bsidesfortwayne-2024-tickets-789388280597&#34;&gt;Eventbrite&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additionally, we are proud to announce training this year from Antisyphon! To register for training please go here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.antisyphontraining.com/event/antisyphon-training-bsides-fort-wayne-2024/&#34;&gt;Antisyphon Training&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2 important notes:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are purchasing a training pass from Antisyphon, training comes with a FREE BSidesFW ticket.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you are a student or in need of a reduced cost ticket with no questions asked, please email &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bsidesfortwayne.tickets@gmail.com&#34;&gt;bsidesfortwayne.tickets@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;. We want you there and we won&amp;rsquo;t let cost stand in the way of that!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Tickets for BSidesFortWayne are available now! The regular price is $25.</p>
<p>Grab your ticket at <a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/bsidesfortwayne-2024-tickets-789388280597">Eventbrite</a>!</p>
<p>Additionally, we are proud to announce training this year from Antisyphon! To register for training please go here: <a href="https://www.antisyphontraining.com/event/antisyphon-training-bsides-fort-wayne-2024/">Antisyphon Training</a>!</p>
<p>2 important notes:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<p>If you are purchasing a training pass from Antisyphon, training comes with a FREE BSidesFW ticket.</p>
</li>
<li>
<p>If you are a student or in need of a reduced cost ticket with no questions asked, please email <a href="mailto:bsidesfortwayne.tickets@gmail.com">bsidesfortwayne.tickets@gmail.com</a>. We want you there and we won&rsquo;t let cost stand in the way of that!</p>
</li>
</ol>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>CFP 2024</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2024/02/2024-cfp/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2024/02/2024-cfp/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re accepting talks and workshop ideas for the 3rd annual BSidesFortWayne!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re open to any and all information security topics, it don&amp;rsquo;t matter if you&amp;rsquo;re red or blue. 🎙️🎶&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Application: &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdjRIJL14ykacmtCa9ssQ6G42hOwstufQACNTIn6LJXLCSXrQ/viewform&#34;&gt;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdjRIJL14ykacmtCa9ssQ6G42hOwstufQACNTIn6LJXLCSXrQ/viewform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;connect-with-us&#34;&gt;Connect with us&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne&#34;&gt;https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LinkedIn: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne&#34;&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summit City Infosec Discord Chat Server: &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/tM4eZFFzjg&#34;&gt;https://discord.gg/tM4eZFFzjg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com&#34;&gt;bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We&rsquo;re accepting talks and workshop ideas for the 3rd annual BSidesFortWayne!</p>
<p>We&rsquo;re open to any and all information security topics, it don&rsquo;t matter if you&rsquo;re red or blue. 🎙️🎶</p>
<p>Application: <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdjRIJL14ykacmtCa9ssQ6G42hOwstufQACNTIn6LJXLCSXrQ/viewform">https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdjRIJL14ykacmtCa9ssQ6G42hOwstufQACNTIn6LJXLCSXrQ/viewform</a></p>
<h2 id="connect-with-us">Connect with us</h2>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne">https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne</a></p>
<p>LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne">https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne</a></p>
<p>Summit City Infosec Discord Chat Server: <a href="https://discord.gg/tM4eZFFzjg">https://discord.gg/tM4eZFFzjg</a></p>
<h2 id="questions">Questions</h2>
<p>Email: <a href="mailto:bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com">bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com</a></p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Schedule of Events 2024</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/fwbsides-2024/</link>
            <pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2024 23:46:59 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2024/01/fwbsides-2024/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;CFP &lt;strong&gt;opens February 1st&lt;/strong&gt; and will &lt;strong&gt;close March 15th&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Speakers will be selected and notified on or before &lt;strong&gt;March 22nd&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BSides Fort Wayne on &lt;strong&gt;Saturday, May 4, 2024 at
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sweetwater.com/local/directions/&#34;&gt;Sweetwater Sound&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional information about sponsorships is in the post!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>CFP <strong>opens February 1st</strong> and will <strong>close March 15th</strong>.<br>
Speakers will be selected and notified on or before <strong>March 22nd</strong>.</p>
<p>BSides Fort Wayne on <strong>Saturday, May 4, 2024 at
<a href="https://www.sweetwater.com/local/directions/">Sweetwater Sound</a></strong>.</p>
<p>Additional information about sponsorships is in the post!</p>
<p><strong>SPONSORSHIP OPPORTUNITIES AVAILABLE NOW!</strong></p>
<p>If you or your business would like to become a sponsor of this amazing local
cyber security community event, send an email to
<a href="bsidesfortwayne.sponsorships@gmail.com"><strong>bsidesfortwayne.sponsorships@gmail.com</strong></a>
for mor details.</p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>BSidesFortWayne 2024 Event Schedule</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/schedule/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 11:21:57 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/schedule/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;BSidesFortWayne will take place at Sweetwater Sound on Saturday, &lt;strong&gt;May 4th&lt;/strong&gt;. Doors open and registration begins at &lt;strong&gt;8:00 AM&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;track-1&#34;&gt;Track 1&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Training Room&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Starting time&lt;/th&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Presenter&lt;/th&gt;
          &lt;th style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Presentation&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;8:45 AM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;-&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Event Kickoff - Welcome and thank you&amp;rsquo;s&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;9:00 AM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#john-strand---keynote-presenter&#34;&gt; John Strand &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Keynote&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;10:00 AM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;-&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;BREAK&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;10:30 AM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#matt-hansen&#34;&gt; Matt Hansen &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Beyond No: InfoSec&amp;rsquo;s Role in Enterprise Success&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;11:15 AM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#seif-hateb&#34;&gt; S8f (Seif Hateb) &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Three Musketeers, one of them is Purple&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;12:15 PM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;-&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;LUNCH BREAK&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;1:15 PM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#michael-miller&#34;&gt; Michael Miller &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Building a Detection Engineering Lab at Home&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;2:15 PM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#rob-rodriguez&#34;&gt; Rob Rodriguez &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cutting Through The Noise: Lessons From a Decade of Electronic Warfare&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;2:45 PM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;-&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;BREAK&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;3:00 PM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#steve-saylor&#34;&gt; Steve Saylor &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Winning the Battle for Budget&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;3:45 PM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;//localhost:1313/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#christian-ebel-orr&#34;&gt; Christian Ebel-Orr &lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Cyber Threats and Criminal Trends&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
      &lt;tr&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;5:00 PM&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;-&lt;/td&gt;
          &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center&#34;&gt;Closing Notes / CTF Winners / Raffle&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;track-2&#34;&gt;Track 2&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location:&lt;/strong&gt; Conference Hall 2B &amp;amp; 2C&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>BSidesFortWayne will take place at Sweetwater Sound on Saturday, <strong>May 4th</strong>. Doors open and registration begins at <strong>8:00 AM</strong>.</p>
<h2 id="track-1">Track 1</h2>
<p><strong>Location:</strong> Training Room</p>
<table>
  <thead>
      <tr>
          <th style="text-align: center">Starting time</th>
          <th style="text-align: center">Presenter</th>
          <th style="text-align: center">Presentation</th>
      </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">8:45 AM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">-</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">Event Kickoff - Welcome and thank you&rsquo;s</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">9:00 AM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#john-strand---keynote-presenter"> John Strand </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Keynote</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">10:00 AM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">-</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">BREAK</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">10:30 AM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#matt-hansen"> Matt Hansen </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Beyond No: InfoSec&rsquo;s Role in Enterprise Success</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">11:15 AM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#seif-hateb"> S8f (Seif Hateb) </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>The Three Musketeers, one of them is Purple</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">12:15 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">-</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">LUNCH BREAK</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">1:15 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#michael-miller"> Michael Miller </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Building a Detection Engineering Lab at Home</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">2:15 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#rob-rodriguez"> Rob Rodriguez </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Cutting Through The Noise: Lessons From a Decade of Electronic Warfare</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">2:45 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">-</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">BREAK</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">3:00 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#steve-saylor"> Steve Saylor </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Winning the Battle for Budget</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">3:45 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#christian-ebel-orr"> Christian Ebel-Orr </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Cyber Threats and Criminal Trends</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">5:00 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">-</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">Closing Notes / CTF Winners / Raffle</td>
      </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<h2 id="track-2">Track 2</h2>
<p><strong>Location:</strong> Conference Hall 2B &amp; 2C</p>
<table>
  <thead>
      <tr>
          <th style="text-align: center">Starting time</th>
          <th style="text-align: center">Presenter</th>
          <th style="text-align: center">Presentation</th>
      </tr>
  </thead>
  <tbody>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">10:30 AM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#0ddj0bb"> 0DDJ0BB </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Nothing Went to Plan&hellip;.. Because You Didn&rsquo;t Have a Plan</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">11:15 AM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#dale-fay-and-meredith-russell-fay"> Dale Fay and Meredith Russell-Fay </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Hack Your Mind: Practical Mental Health Insights for Technical People</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">11:45 AM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#richard-rieben"> Richard Rieben </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>The Audit: A Significant Emotional Event</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">12:15 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">-</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">LUNCH BREAK (FOOD IN TRAINING HALL)</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">1:15 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#alissa-dnsprincess"> Alissa - (DNSPrincess) </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Preventing and Recovering from Burnout</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">2:15 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#stephen-heindel"> Stephen Heindel </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Leveling Up Your Scripting</em></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">2:45 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">-</td>
          <td style="text-align: center">BREAK</td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
          <td style="text-align: center">3:00 PM</td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><a href="/posts/2024/04/speakers-2024#harish-santhanalakshmi-ganesan"> Harish Santhanalakshmi Ganesan  </a></td>
          <td style="text-align: center"><em>Hacking AI/ML for fun and profit</em></td>
      </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<h2 id="alternate-tracks">Alternate Tracks</h2>
<h3 id="ctf--badge-hacking--lock-picking-village">CTF / Badge Hacking / Lock Picking Village</h3>
<p><strong>Location:</strong> Conference Hall 2A<br>
<strong>When:</strong> 10 AM - 4:00 PM</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Speakers 2023</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/speakers-2023/</link>
            <pubDate>Thu, 27 Apr 2023 11:32:37 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2023/04/speakers-2023/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Come take a look at our exciting list of experts, leaders, and practitioners who are going to give us an amazing conference. If you haven’t bought your ticket yet, you will want to after this!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Come take a look at our exciting list of experts, leaders, and practitioners who are going to give us an amazing conference. If you haven’t bought your ticket yet, you will want to after this!</p>
<h2 id="bb-king---keynote-speaker">BB King - Keynote Speaker</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/BB%20King.png"
    alt="BB King picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="keynote-">Keynote: <em>&ldquo;AI is changing your world, but you will still matter&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Brian &ldquo;BB&rdquo; King, GXPN, CEPT, CISSP, GCIH, GCIA<br>
BB has been a Security Consultant at Black Hills Informatin Security since 2015 and a penetration tester since 2008. In previous corporate security roles, he developed application security testing and reporting standards, worked with development teams to improve coding practices, and with new penetration testers to help them gain proficiency and understanding. At BHIS, he specializes in web applications and web APIs, and sees developers and QA engineers as partners in the never-ending quest to make security part of the development lifecycle instead of just a checkpoint near the end. He teaches penetration testing and reporting classes with Antisyphon Training and at local security conferences whenever he can.</p>
<h2 id="carrie-roberts">Carrie Roberts</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Carrie%20Roberts.jpg"
    alt="Carrie Roberts picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation-">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;10 Hacks to Bypass PowerShell History Log&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Carrie Roberts is a programmer, turned pentester, turned red teamer, turned blue-ish purple. She is currently a Defense Engineer at Walmart. She loves to learn and give back to the community. She is one of the primary Atomic Red Team project maintainers and developers and has developed many of her own open-source tools. She holds master’s Degrees in both Computer Science and Information Security Engineering. She has earned 12 GIAC certifications including the prestigious “Security Expert” (GSE) certification.</p>
<h2 id="bryan-sears">Bryan Sears</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Bryan%20Sears.jpg"
    alt="Bryan Sears picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--1">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;5 Things to do before your next pentest&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Bryan Sears is a cyber security engineer for Shorepoint inc where he travels the county performing Penetration Test for customers. He is OSCP and CRTO I certified. Bryan is also currently working on his Master&rsquo;s in Information Security and Information Assurance from WGU. Bryan is also an licensed Official for High School football and Wrestling. While not comprising active directory, He enjoys exploring the trails on his bike or with his Dog.</p>
<h2 id="edmund-brumaghin">Edmund Brumaghin</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Edmund%20Brumaghin.jpg"
    alt="Edmund Brumaghin picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--2">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;IPFS, DApps, &amp; Blockchains: How Web3 Technologies Are Being Abused In Malware and Phishing Campaigns&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Edmund Brumaghin is a threat researcher with Cisco Talos. He has spent the past several years protecting environments across several different industries including nuclear energy, financial services, etc. He currently spends his days hunting malware and analyzing various threats as they emerge and continue to evolve. In his time with Talos he has researched ransomware, banking trojans and other threats being distributed using various attack vectors. He has also worked to expose large scale malware campaigns and raise awareness of security threats observed across the threat landscape.</p>
<h2 id="michael-miller">Michael Miller</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Michael%20Miller.jpg"
    alt="Michael Miller picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--3">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Building Home Labs for Fun &amp; Career Development&rdquo;</em></h5>
<h5 id="presentation--4">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Let’s Talk About Bruno - The Reality of the Cybersecurity Talent Shortage&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Michael is a cybersecurity leader &amp; practitioner with 11+ years&rsquo; experience in enterprise cybersecurity, networking, server administration, and programming. Specializing in security architecture, engineering, automation, and operations, he has a proven record of improving team organization, morale, and enhancing cross functional team collaboration while continuously increasing overall company security maturity. Passionately focused on attracting, developing, and retaining talent, he advocates improving diversity, equity, and inclusion in both his teams and the cybersecurity industry. He has a B.S. in Cybersecurity and Information Assurance from WGU, and an A.A.B. in Network Administration and Computer Programming from NSCC where he also sits as a member of the IT advisory board. Michael holds a variety of industry certifications including the CCSP, SSCP, CySA+, CEH, and ECES just to name a few. Michael lives in Northwest Ohio with his wife and their two children. In his free time, he enjoys spending time with his family, cooking (especially grilling), working on home improvement projects, reading, and working in his home networking lab.</p>
<h2 id="kent-backman">Kent Backman</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Kent%20Backman.jpeg"
    alt="Kent Backman picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--5">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Inside Black Basta Exfiltration Operations&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Kent Backman is a Principal Adversary Hunter at Dragos, specializing in behind-keyboard adversaries to industrial control systems and operational technology. Kent’s expertise has been informed by incident response, digital forensics, threat analysis, and hunting work for government and commercial organizations since 2002.</p>
<h2 id="matt-fisher--wren-forfa">Matt Fisher &amp; Wren Forfa</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Matt%20Fisher%20and%20Wren%20Forfa.jpg"
    alt="Matt Fisher &amp; Wren Forfa picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--6">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;The Red and the Blue: A Dual-Sided Analysis of DNS Tunnelling&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Matthew Fisher and Renee (Wren) Forfa graduated from Purdue University in May of 2023 with degrees in Cybersecurity. Matthew studied a second major in Network Engineering Technology, while Wren received a second degree in Russian. They are both commissioned officers in the Department of the Air Force. Matthew has operational and leadership experience in the cyber world as a Security Analyst and from his time at a federally funded research center. Wren has hands-on teaching experience and has researched topics spanning from &ldquo;Malware Identification and Analysis&rdquo; to &ldquo;Linguistic Changes in Russian in Turbulent Times&rdquo;. Matt and Wren enjoy going camping, playing videogames, and going to the gym!</p>
<p>Fun fact: They got engaged this Spring!</p>
<h2 id="seif-hateb">Seif Hateb</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Seif%20Hateb.png"
    alt="Seif Hateb picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--7">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Purple Teaming For All&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Seif Hateb is a Security Architect with a passion for excellence and innovation. For over a decade, Seif has been designing and delivering cutting-edge security solutions in the fields of cyber defense, cryptography, security architecture, purple teaming, telco, and OT security. Seif has worked on various projects in the Telecommunications and Healthcare industries, ensuring compliance, risk management, and business continuity.
Seif a black belt in judo, which taught him discipline, resilience, and teamwork. Seif is a life-long learner who constantly seeks new challenges and opportunities to grow. Seif is also a mentor, a security professor, and a trainer who loves to share my knowledge and experience with others.</p>
<p>Seif collaborates with diverse teams and stakeholders to design and implement cloud and application security architectures that align with business goals and industry standards. Seif is always eager to learn new technologies and best practices to enhance my expertise and contribute to the security community.</p>
<h2 id="curtis-brazzell">Curtis Brazzell</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Curtis%20Brazzell.jpg"
    alt="Curtis Brazzell picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--8">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;These Aren&rsquo;t the Phish You&rsquo;re Looking For&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Curtis is a local security professional with 17 years of security experience. He holds a CISSP, is the author of the Cybersecurity ABC’s children’s books, and is a researcher and blogger in his free time. He’s provided many defensive and offensive security services for customers over the last 12 years and has a passion for spear-phishing and awareness training.</p>
<h2 id="matt-hansen">Matt Hansen</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Matt%20Hansen.jpg"
    alt="Matt Hansen picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--9">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;The Journey to Big Tech, from a Small Town&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Matt is a Cloud Solution Architect at Microsoft who focuses on Azure Infrastructure and Security. He has been in the industry for 15 years as an Engineer and Architect, and serves as a Subject Matter Expert, Advisory Committee Member, and as a Professor for Cloud and Security Technologies. Matt holds over 50 industry certifications such as the CCSP, CISSP, Azure Security Engineer, Azure Network Engineer, and has held all versions of the Azure Solutions Architecture Certifications. Matt holds a B.S in Network Engineering and M.S in Engineering Management, and a M.S in Information Systems Security and an Executive Certificate in Cybersecurity Management.</p>
<h2 id="tj-patterson">TJ Patterson</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/TJ%20Patterson.jpg"
    alt="TJ Patterson picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--10">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Practical Vulnerability Management&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>T.J. is an accomplished leader in information security, possessing 15 years of industry experience. He has performed different roles across multiple technical disciplines, providing design, implementation and support of a wide variety of technologies.</p>
<p>While he enjoys finding creative ways to solve complex problems, T.J. is most passionate about developing other practitioners. He also is driven by the opportunity to influence cybersecurity culture in anyone.</p>
<p>T.J. currently serves as the Information Security Officer for a financial institution and is responsible for its information security strategy and its execution across the organization, including digital and paper assets.</p>
<p>When not in the office, you will find T.J. spending time with his family or studying foreign languages. He also has 13+ years of experience playing the drums, and he has played many other musical instruments since childhood.</p>
<h2 id="chris-saylor">Chris Saylor</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Chris%20Saylor.jpg"
    alt="Chris Saylor picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--11">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Building a Security Governance Program&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Chris has been in the IT/IS fields about for 25 years, and concentrated in consulting services for the finance and healthcare industries before taking on the Information Security Officer role for Bippus State Bank in 2018.</p>
<h2 id="christian-ebel-orr">Christian Ebel-Orr</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Christian%20Ebel-Orr.jpg"
    alt="Christian Ebel-Orr picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--12">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Cyber Threats and Criminal Trends&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Special Agent Christian Ebel-Orr has been with the Secret Service for 20 years. During that time, he has been assigned to the Counter Assault Team, Presidential Protective Detail, Obama Protective Detail, and the Indianapolis Field Office. He currently manages the Indianapolis Computer Forensics Lab and the Indiana Cyber Fraud Task Force. Previously, he was a police officer in Bloomington, IN for five years.</p>
<h2 id="chris-harvey">Chris Harvey</h2>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2023/Chris%20Harvey.jpg"
    alt="Chris Harvey picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h5 id="presentation--13">Presentation: <em>&ldquo;Planting a Tree: The long-game of aligning with the business for support, funding, and staff&rdquo;</em></h5>
<p>Christopher Harvey is the Assistant Vice President of Technology Architecture and the Chief Information Security Officer (CISO) at Brotherhood Mutual Insurance Company. He has been with Brotherhood Mutual since 1998 and has earned the CPCU designation (Chartered Property Casualty Underwriter). Chris holds a Management Information Systems degree from Ball State University, and is a graduate of General Electric’s ISMP program. He has technical certifications from Microsoft, Novell, Lotus, IBM, and is a Certified Information Security Manager (CISM).<br>
Today Chris oversees various teams at Brotherhood Mutual including Infrastructure, Support Desk, Office Services, Business Intelligence, andDevOps. In his role as CISO, he focuses on ensuring the stability, security, and performance of the company’s information systems. This includes primary oversight of networking, data security, communication services, computer equipment, cloud, and application servers.</p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Tickets Available 2023</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/tickets-available-2023/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 09:00:24 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2023/03/tickets-available-2023/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Tickets for BSidesFortWayne are available now! The regular price is $25, and students can get a discount down to $10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grab your ticket at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/bsidesfortwayne-2023-tickets-559672183567&#34;&gt;Eventbrite&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each ticket will include: BSidesFortWayne T-shirt, lunch, program, lanyard, and badge!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Students who wish to receive the discount should contact us at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bsidesfortwayne.tickets@gmail.com&#34;&gt;bsidesfortwayne.tickets@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; to receive a promo code.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Tickets for BSidesFortWayne are available now! The regular price is $25, and students can get a discount down to $10.</p>
<p>Grab your ticket at <a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/bsidesfortwayne-2023-tickets-559672183567">Eventbrite</a>!</p>
<p>Each ticket will include: BSidesFortWayne T-shirt, lunch, program, lanyard, and badge!</p>
<p>Students who wish to receive the discount should contact us at <a href="mailto:bsidesfortwayne.tickets@gmail.com">bsidesfortwayne.tickets@gmail.com</a> to receive a promo code.</p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>CFP 2023</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/cfp-2023/</link>
            <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 07:14:03 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/cfp-2023/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re accepting talks and workshop ideas for the 2nd annual BSidesFortWayne!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re open to any and all information security topics, it don&amp;rsquo;t matter if you&amp;rsquo;re red or blue. 🎙️🎶&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Application: &lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScPwg7mlVl3OT_2TrDOwhrBomHWZXK1Qyc6Ka0CrvFfPM0a3Q/viewform&#34;&gt;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScPwg7mlVl3OT_2TrDOwhrBomHWZXK1Qyc6Ka0CrvFfPM0a3Q/viewform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;connect-with-us&#34;&gt;Connect with us&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne&#34;&gt;https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;LinkedIn: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne&#34;&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Summit City Infosec Discord Chat Server: &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/tM4eZFFzjg&#34;&gt;https://discord.gg/tM4eZFFzjg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com&#34;&gt;bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We&rsquo;re accepting talks and workshop ideas for the 2nd annual BSidesFortWayne!</p>
<p>We&rsquo;re open to any and all information security topics, it don&rsquo;t matter if you&rsquo;re red or blue. 🎙️🎶</p>
<p>Application: <a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScPwg7mlVl3OT_2TrDOwhrBomHWZXK1Qyc6Ka0CrvFfPM0a3Q/viewform">https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLScPwg7mlVl3OT_2TrDOwhrBomHWZXK1Qyc6Ka0CrvFfPM0a3Q/viewform</a></p>
<h2 id="connect-with-us">Connect with us</h2>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne">https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne</a></p>
<p>LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne">https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne</a></p>
<p>Summit City Infosec Discord Chat Server: <a href="https://discord.gg/tM4eZFFzjg">https://discord.gg/tM4eZFFzjg</a></p>
<h2 id="questions">Questions</h2>
<p>Email: <a href="mailto:bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com">bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com</a></p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Schedule of Events 2023</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/schedule-of-events-2023/</link>
            <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 10:08:04 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2023/01/schedule-of-events-2023/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;CFP &lt;strong&gt;opens January 27th&lt;/strong&gt; and will &lt;strong&gt;close March 17th&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Speakers will be selected and notified on or before &lt;strong&gt;March 24th&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Registration for BSides Fort Wayne 2023 opens &lt;strong&gt;March 31st&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Regular registration includes a t-shirt and &lt;strong&gt;closes May 1st&lt;/strong&gt; or until sold
out, whichever comes first.&lt;br&gt;
Late registration (attendance only) closes the day before the BSides Fort Wayne
event.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BSides Fort Wayne on &lt;strong&gt;Saturday, May 20, 2023 at
&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sweetwater.com/local/directions/&#34;&gt;Sweetwater Sound&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Additional information about sponsorships is in the post!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>CFP <strong>opens January 27th</strong> and will <strong>close March 17th</strong>.<br>
Speakers will be selected and notified on or before <strong>March 24th</strong>.<br>
Registration for BSides Fort Wayne 2023 opens <strong>March 31st</strong>.<br>
Regular registration includes a t-shirt and <strong>closes May 1st</strong> or until sold
out, whichever comes first.<br>
Late registration (attendance only) closes the day before the BSides Fort Wayne
event.</p>
<p>BSides Fort Wayne on <strong>Saturday, May 20, 2023 at
<a href="https://www.sweetwater.com/local/directions/">Sweetwater Sound</a></strong>.</p>
<p>Additional information about sponsorships is in the post!</p>
<p><strong>SPONSORSHIP OPPORTUNITIES AVAILABLE NOW!</strong></p>
<p>If you or your business would like to become a sponsor of this amazing local
cyber security community event, send an email to
<a href="bsidesfortwayne.sponsorships@gmail.com"><strong>bsidesfortwayne.sponsorships@gmail.com</strong></a>
for mor details.</p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>BSides CTF is Live!</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/05/ctf-is-live/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 10:03:36 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/05/ctf-is-live/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;The BSides CTF has started! You can access it here: &lt;a href=&#34;https://ctf.bsidesfortwayne.org/&#34;&gt;https://ctf.bsidesfortwayne.org/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To join, you need the Registration Code that is located in CTF room (Conference Hall 2C).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The BSides CTF has started! You can access it here: <a href="https://ctf.bsidesfortwayne.org/">https://ctf.bsidesfortwayne.org/</a></p>
<p>To join, you need the Registration Code that is located in CTF room (Conference Hall 2C).</p>
<p>Good luck!</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Conference is Live!</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/05/conference-is-live/</link>
            <pubDate>Sat, 21 May 2022 09:20:59 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/05/conference-is-live/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;BSides Fort Wayne has officially started! If you cannot join us in person, please join our &lt;a href=&#34;https://sweetwater.zoom.us/j/87881455753?pwd=eFZYQ2h5YWJtT2dEdldpNXF0Z1FPZz09&#34;&gt;Zoom stream&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Feel free to join our &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/kdHU84mUNF&#34;&gt;Discord server&lt;/a&gt; to chat with other participants!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>BSides Fort Wayne has officially started! If you cannot join us in person, please join our <a href="https://sweetwater.zoom.us/j/87881455753?pwd=eFZYQ2h5YWJtT2dEdldpNXF0Z1FPZz09">Zoom stream</a>!</p>
<p>Feel free to join our <a href="https://discord.gg/kdHU84mUNF">Discord server</a> to chat with other participants!</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Keynotes and Presenters 2022</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/04/speakers_2022/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Apr 2022 14:30:28 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/04/speakers_2022/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Come take a look at our exciting list of experts, leaders, and practitioners who are going to give us an amazing conference. If you haven’t bought your ticket yet, you will want to after this!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Come take a look at our exciting list of experts, leaders, and practitioners who are going to give us an amazing conference. If you haven’t bought your ticket yet, you will want to after this!</p>
<h2 id="keynotes">Keynotes</h2>
<h3 id="ira-winkler">Ira Winkler</h3>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2022/ira_winkler.png"
    alt="Ira Winkler picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h6 id="opening-keynote-human-security-engineering-stopping-the-myth-of-the-human-firewall">Opening Keynote: <em>“Human Security Engineering: Stopping the myth of the human firewall”</em></h6>
<p>Ira Winkler, CISSP is Chief Security Architect for Walmart and author of You Can Stop Stupid and Security Awareness for Dummies.  He is considered one of the world’s most influential security professionals, and has been named a “Modern Day James Bond” by the media.  He did this by performing espionage simulations, where he physically and technically “broke into” some of the largest companies in the World and investigating crimes against them, and telling them how to cost effectively protect their information and computer infrastructure.  He continues to perform these espionage simulations, as well as assisting organizations in developing cost effective security programs.  Ira also won the Hall of Fame award from the Information Systems Security Association, as well as several other prestigious industry awards. CSO Magazine named Ira a CSO Compass Award winner as The Awareness Crusader. Most recently, Ira was named 2021 Top Cybersecurity Leader by Security Magazine.</p>
<h3 id="dr-chris-fennell">Dr. Chris Fennell</h3>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2022/dr_chris_fennell.png"
    alt="Dr. Chris Fennell picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h6 id="closing-keynote-using-open-source-algorithms-for-c2-beacon-detection-with-microsoft-sentinel">Closing Keynote: <em>“Using open source algorithms for C2 beacon detection with Microsoft Sentinel”</em></h6>
<p>Chris Fennell is a cybersecurity researcher with Walmart Information Security who studies how individuals use and interact with security technologies. He has a PhD in Information from Michigan State University and feels blessed to have worked with some amazing researchers and practitioners in the cybersecurity community. He has worked on multiple National Science Foundation grants as well as working at a federally funded research center a part of the Department of Defense. He is passionate about security and is interested in exploring its economic, social and policy impacts.</p>
<h2 id="presenters">Presenters</h2>
<h3 id="josh-brower">Josh Brower</h3>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2022/josh_brower.jpg"
    alt="Josh Brower picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h6 id="presentation-applying-sysmon-type-prefiltering-to-osquery-process-auditing">Presentation: <em>“Applying Sysmon-type prefiltering to Osquery Process Auditing”</em></h6>
<p>Josh Brower has been crashing computers since his teens, and now feels fortunate to be doing it professionally. He has spent the last 15 years focusing on InfoSec, particularly network and endpoint detection. He also enjoys teaching around InfoSec issues, especially to non-technical learners - helping them to understand how their actions in the digital world have real-world consequences, as well as how to proactively reduce the risk.</p>
<h3 id="aaron-foster">Aaron Foster</h3>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2022/aaron_foster.jpeg"
    alt="Aaron Foster picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h6 id="presentation-encrypted-traffic-and-the-modern-firewall">Presentation: <em>“Encrypted Traffic and the Modern Firewall”</em></h6>
<p>Aaron is a Senior Network Engineer working in the managed security services space.  He achieved his CCIE Collaboration in 2014 and has more than 15 years of experience in the IT sector.  Aaron has extensive experience deploying and managing network security technologies across multiple vendors and verticals. When not at work, he enjoys cycling, woodworking, and building with Lego.</p>
<script type="text/art">
bsftw{JustWgetItAndGrepForTheFlagMate!}
</script>
<h3 id="carrie-roberts">Carrie Roberts</h3>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2022/carrie_roberts.jpg"
    alt="Carrie Roberts picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h6 id="presentation-atomic-red-team-hands-on-getting-started-guide">Presentation: <em>“Atomic Red Team: Hands-on Getting Started Guide”</em></h6>
<p>Carrie Roberts is a web application developer, turned pentester, turned red teamer, turned blue. She loves to learn and give back to the community. She is currently one of the primary Atomic Red Team project maintainers and developers and has developed many of her own open source tools including the Domain Password Audit Tool (DPAT) and Slack Extract. She holds master’s Degrees in both Computer Science and Information Security Engineering. She has earned 12 GIAC certifications including the prestigious “Security Expert” (GSE) certification. She has spoken at numerous security conferences including DerbyCon and Wild West Hackin’ Fest, published many blog posts on topics ranging from social engineering to bypassing anti-virus, and contributed new research on the VBA Stomping maldoc technique. She is currently a Defense Engineer at Walmart.</p>
<h3 id="mike-everett">Mike Everett</h3>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2022/mike_everett.jpg"
    alt="Mike Everett picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h6 id="presentation-understanding-how-ransomware-has-become-big-business">Presentation: <em>“Understanding how Ransomware has become big business!”</em></h6>
<p>Mike has over 25 years of experience in the IT industry across three major sectors: Government, Healthcare and Financial Services. Mike spent his last 12 years working with the Farm Credit Association. Spending the past 9.5 years as their VP Chief Security Officer. During his tenure there, he led many different initiatives across database systems, infrastructure and security. Most notable he led their database systems team in delivering their first ever data warehouse to include data mining and analytics. Mike also led the initiative to build out their data center upon the association purchasing a 178,000 sq ft new corporate office. Included, wireless, collaboration, storage, cooling and anything else involved with infrastructure, network and security, to include physical security. During his tenure, he was always the CSO, leading all initiatives around Cybersecurity, architecture, compliance, risk and incident response.</p>
<p>Prior to joining Farm Credit, Mike worked 11 years in Healthcare for Catholic Health Initiatives. He specialized in database systems, architecture, business continuity, compliance, privacy, security and change management.</p>
<p>Mike also spent 3 years in the government sector with a focus on data analytics.</p>
<h3 id="rod-trent">Rod Trent</h3>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2022/rod_trent.jpg"
    alt="Rod Trent picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h6 id="presentation-building-efficiency-in-the-soc-using-microsoft-sentinel">Presentation: <em>“Building Efficiency in the SOC Using Microsoft Sentinel”</em></h6>
<p>Rod Trent is a Cloud Security Advocate for Microsoft and a Microsoft Sentinel global SME. He is a husband, dad, and first-time grandfather (so speak slow and loud). He spends his spare time (if such a thing does truly exist) simultaneously watching Six Million Dollar Man TV show episodes and writing KQL queries.</p>
<h3 id="bb-king">BB King</h3>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2022/bb_king.jpg"
    alt="BB King picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h6 id="presentation-secret-burp-suite-secrets">Presentation: <em>“Secret Burp Suite Secrets”</em></h6>
<p>Brian (BB) King began working for Black Hills Information Security (BHIS) as a Security Consultant in 2015. His IT career started with telephone technical support, transitioned to supporting software dev toolkits, and eventually leading a team focused on testing internal applications during corporate mergers. In 2008, he moved to information security, where he developed application security testing and reporting standards, before becoming a security analyst. To this day, Brian loves the work environment and how BHIS exceeds his expectations in different ways. Outside of work, Brian raises service dogs for Canine Companions for Independence, likes to brew beers, and carpentry.</p>
<h3 id="matthew-fisher">Matthew Fisher</h3>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2022/matthew_fisher.png"
    alt="Matthew Fisher picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h6 id="presentation-solution-to-a-high-school-no-phone-policy-written-in-batch">Presentation: <em>“Solution to a High School No Phone Policy Written in Batch.”</em></h6>
<p>Matthew Fisher is a Purdue University student studying cybersecurity, network engineering, and the Russian language. He is part of the Air Force ROTC program at Purdue, serving as the director of space operations at Purdue’s AFROTC detachment. After graduating, Matthew will commission into the United States Air Force, looking to become a Cyberspace Effects Operations officer. While studying, Matthew works part time as a Jr. System Administrator at Ruoff Mortgage, with a focus on Ansible development for deploying web projects. In his free time, he enjoys video games and powerlifting.</p>
<h3 id="jake-butler">Jake Butler</h3>
<figure><img src="/img/speakers2022/jake_butler.jpg"
    alt="Jake Butler picture" width="70%">
</figure>

<h6 id="presentation-building-a-cyber-program-with-a-framework">Presentation: <em>“Building a Cyber program with a Framework”</em></h6>
<p>Jake Butler is a leading expert on IT infrastructure, security, and compliance with over 20 years of experience in IT Security and operations. Jake is a frequent speaker on topics including security breaches, threats, big data analytics, audit and compliance, and IT forensics. Jake is serving as a board member for InfraGard Indiana Members Alliance as well as the Co-Chair to the Indiana Executive Council on Cybersecurity. He managed the Information Technology Security team for 10+ years, where he was able to advance them through several iterations of compliance measures.</p>
<p>Jake has obtained his CISSP, C|EH, C|HFI, and several other vendor-specific certifications related to Cybersecurity. Jake’s educational background is a Master of Science in Cybersecurity and Information Assurance with WGU.</p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Tickets Available!</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/03/tickets-available/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 29 Mar 2022 09:35:29 -0400</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/03/tickets-available/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;The tickets for BSidesFortWayne are available now! The regular price is $25, and students can get a discount down to $10.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Grab your ticket now at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.eventbrite.com/e/bsidesfortwayne-tickets-307893928027&#34;&gt;Eventbrite&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each ticket will include: BSidesFortWayne T-shirt, lunch, program, lanyard, and badge!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Students who wish to receive the discount should contact us at &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com&#34;&gt;bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; to receive a promo code.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>The tickets for BSidesFortWayne are available now! The regular price is $25, and students can get a discount down to $10.</p>
<p>Grab your ticket now at <a href="https://www.eventbrite.com/e/bsidesfortwayne-tickets-307893928027">Eventbrite</a>!</p>
<p>Each ticket will include: BSidesFortWayne T-shirt, lunch, program, lanyard, and badge!</p>
<p>Students who wish to receive the discount should contact us at <a href="mailto:bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com">bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com</a> to receive a promo code.</p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Call For Papers</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/02/cfp/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 01 Feb 2022 13:03:58 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/02/cfp/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re ready to start accepting talks and workshop ideas for the first BSidesFortWayne!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re open to any and all information security topics, it don&amp;rsquo;t matter if you&amp;rsquo;re red or blue. 🎙️🎶&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdCN90FCIxWH98C3WENPQy6lJKFHR51q_DRrnlN-o0edebfjw/viewform&#34;&gt;https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdCN90FCIxWH98C3WENPQy6lJKFHR51q_DRrnlN-o0edebfjw/viewform&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;connect-with-us&#34;&gt;Connect with us!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne&#34;&gt;https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
LinkedIn: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne&#34;&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Summit City Infosec Discord Chat Server: &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/kdHU84mUNF&#34;&gt;https://discord.gg/kdHU84mUNF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com&#34;&gt;bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>We&rsquo;re ready to start accepting talks and workshop ideas for the first BSidesFortWayne!</p>
<p>We&rsquo;re open to any and all information security topics, it don&rsquo;t matter if you&rsquo;re red or blue. 🎙️🎶</p>
<p><a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdCN90FCIxWH98C3WENPQy6lJKFHR51q_DRrnlN-o0edebfjw/viewform">https://docs.google.com/forms/d/e/1FAIpQLSdCN90FCIxWH98C3WENPQy6lJKFHR51q_DRrnlN-o0edebfjw/viewform</a></p>
<h2 id="connect-with-us">Connect with us!</h2>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne">https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne</a><br>
LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne">https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne</a><br>
Summit City Infosec Discord Chat Server: <a href="https://discord.gg/kdHU84mUNF">https://discord.gg/kdHU84mUNF</a></p>
<h2 id="questions">Questions?</h2>
<p>Email: <a href="mailto:bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com">bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com</a></p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>About</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/01/about/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:42:58 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/01/about/</guid>
            <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-is-bsides&#34;&gt;What is BSides?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Each BSides is a community-driven framework for building events for and by information security community members.  The goal is to expand the spectrum of conversation beyond the traditional confines of space and time.  It creates opportunities for individuals to both present and participate in an intimate atmosphere that encourages collaboration. It is an intense event with discussions, demos, and interaction from participants. It is where conversations for the next-big-thing are happening.&lt;br&gt;
For more on BSides: &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.securitybsides.com/&#34;&gt;http://www.securitybsides.com/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-is-bsidesfortwayne&#34;&gt;What is BSidesFortWayne?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;BSidesFortWayne started as a conversation amongst friends with the desire to see an information security conference right here in our city. &amp;ldquo;Better Together&amp;rdquo; is a theme for our local conference. When we connect with other information security professionals and share our knowledge openly, we can each better secure ourselves and the organizations that we help protect. We&amp;rsquo;re also extremely excited to see how this can open up new opportunities for organizations to find talent and for folks that are wanting to break into the information security industry to gain knowledge and make connections with people that may help propel them into the industry.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;connect-with-us&#34;&gt;Connect with us!&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne&#34;&gt;https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
LinkedIn: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne&#34;&gt;https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br&gt;
Summit City Infosec Discord Chat Server: &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/kdHU84mUNF&#34;&gt;https://discord.gg/kdHU84mUNF&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;questions&#34;&gt;Questions?&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Email: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com&#34;&gt;bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="what-is-bsides">What is BSides?</h1>
<p>Each BSides is a community-driven framework for building events for and by information security community members.  The goal is to expand the spectrum of conversation beyond the traditional confines of space and time.  It creates opportunities for individuals to both present and participate in an intimate atmosphere that encourages collaboration. It is an intense event with discussions, demos, and interaction from participants. It is where conversations for the next-big-thing are happening.<br>
For more on BSides: <a href="http://www.securitybsides.com/">http://www.securitybsides.com/</a></p>
<h1 id="what-is-bsidesfortwayne">What is BSidesFortWayne?</h1>
<p>BSidesFortWayne started as a conversation amongst friends with the desire to see an information security conference right here in our city. &ldquo;Better Together&rdquo; is a theme for our local conference. When we connect with other information security professionals and share our knowledge openly, we can each better secure ourselves and the organizations that we help protect. We&rsquo;re also extremely excited to see how this can open up new opportunities for organizations to find talent and for folks that are wanting to break into the information security industry to gain knowledge and make connections with people that may help propel them into the industry.</p>
<h2 id="connect-with-us">Connect with us!</h2>
<p>Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne">https://twitter.com/BSidesFortWayne</a><br>
LinkedIn: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne">https://www.linkedin.com/company/bsidesfortwayne</a><br>
Summit City Infosec Discord Chat Server: <a href="https://discord.gg/kdHU84mUNF">https://discord.gg/kdHU84mUNF</a></p>
<h2 id="questions">Questions?</h2>
<p>Email: <a href="mailto:bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com">bsidesfortwayne@gmail.com</a></p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Schedule of Events</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/01/schedule_of_events/</link>
            <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jan 2022 14:31:06 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2022/01/schedule_of_events/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;Call For Papers opens &lt;strong&gt;February 1st&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Call For Papers closes &lt;strong&gt;March 22nd&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Speakers selected and notified on or before &lt;strong&gt;March 24th&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Registration opens &lt;strong&gt;March 28th&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Regular registration (includes t-shirt) closes &lt;strong&gt;May 1st&lt;/strong&gt; or until sold out, whichever is sooner.&lt;br&gt;
Late registration (attendance only) closes the day before BSidesFortWayne.&lt;br&gt;
BSidesFortWayne – Saturday, &lt;strong&gt;May 21&lt;/strong&gt; at Sweetwater Sound.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Call For Papers opens <strong>February 1st</strong>.<br>
Call For Papers closes <strong>March 22nd</strong>.<br>
Speakers selected and notified on or before <strong>March 24th</strong>.<br>
Registration opens <strong>March 28th</strong>.<br>
Regular registration (includes t-shirt) closes <strong>May 1st</strong> or until sold out, whichever is sooner.<br>
Late registration (attendance only) closes the day before BSidesFortWayne.<br>
BSidesFortWayne – Saturday, <strong>May 21</strong> at Sweetwater Sound.</p>]]></content>
        </item>
        
        <item>
            <title>Coming Soon!</title>
            <link>//localhost:1313/posts/2021/11/coming-soon/</link>
            <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 23:34:53 -0500</pubDate>
            
            <guid>//localhost:1313/posts/2021/11/coming-soon/</guid>
            <description>&lt;p&gt;BSIDES Fort Wayne is coming soon. Check back for updates!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
            <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>BSIDES Fort Wayne is coming soon. Check back for updates!</p>
]]></content>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
